Even if it was a hoax for the sake of
bringing attention to this, that's
low-key noble.
>> If it was a hoax, what do you think is
the correct punishment? And do or do you
think he should be
>> think a murderer is on probation? G.
>> Sure. Sure. I'm asking about Justice
Smlette. I'm asking about that because
you said it was lowkey noble. I just
want
>> literally should be like
>> he should be applauded.
>> Damn.
>> I think
>> Why aren't they bringing charges against
all the white people that call the cops
for BS every single day? So the only
thing I just want to avoid, we cannot
put a culture out there where it becomes
harder for us to believe victims that
this has really happened to
>> and and I don't think it's okay to stage
a hate crime.
>> We can't ever do that.
>> What do you think should happen?
>> I I think that if he 3 years sounds
about right, but some things have to be
done. I feel like they should figure out
if it happened or if it didn't cuz
that's honestly
>> You think this man should be in prison
for 3 years for a hate for a hoax for?
>> First of all, we know that if he was
actually in prison for 3 years, he's not
going to do three years. I think that he
>> You said three years sounds about right.
If you stage a hate crime,